Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
you've got your luggage.
لقد أحضرت أمتعتك.
Are we heading to the airport now?
هل نتجه إلى المطار الآن؟
Yes, let's go.
نعم، هيا بنا.
Have you got your passport?
هل لديك جواز سفرك؟
Lin Mojiao has married Lan Hewei.
تزوج لين موجياو من لان هيوي.
What more do you want from me?
ماذا تريد مني أكثر من ذلك؟
Do you know
هل تعلم
how much I sacrificed
كم ضحيت
for this marriage?
لهذا الزواج؟
And what's the result?
وماذا كانت النتيجة؟
You ruined everything.
لقد أفسدت كل شيء.
What does it have to do with me?
ما علاقة هذا بي؟
You made the wrong move yourself,
لقد اتخذت أنت الخطوة الخاطئة،
and you blame me?
وأنت تلومني؟
How dare you talk back?
كيف تجرؤ على الرد عليّ؟
Lin Mojiao won't do,
لن أقبل بلين موجياو،
there are other groups in Haicheng.
توجد مجموعات أخرى في هايتشنغ.
Your marriage is not a game,
زواجك ليس لعبة،
it's a matter of family.
إنها مسألة عائلية.
A matter of family?
مسألة عائلية؟
I'm just a pawn
أنا مجرد بيدق
for your group's interests.
لمصالح مجموعتكم.
Shut up!
اسكت!
Am I wrong?
هل أنا مخطئ؟
I'm just a pawn for you.
أنا مجرد بيدق في يدك.
I quit.
لقد استقلت.
Stop.
قف.
Don't think I don't know
لا تظن أنني لا أعرف
you have a man outside.
يوجد رجل بالخارج.
I'm telling you.
أقول لك.
Some people can be played with,
يمكن التلاعب ببعض الناس،
but if they affect the interests of the family,
لكن إذا أثرت على مصالح الأسرة،
I will definitely make them disappear.
سأجعلهم يختفون بالتأكيد.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Your last name is Zhu.
اسم عائلتك هو تشو.
Do your job well.
أتقن عملك.
Why am I here?
لماذا أنا هنا؟
Mr. Zhen brought you back.
أعادك السيد زين.
No.
لا.
It's too dangerous for Vivi
الأمر خطير للغاية بالنسبة لـ فيفي
to be alone with that jerk.
أن أكون وحدي مع ذلك الأحمق.
You mean...
تقصد...
You've failed.
لقد فشلت.
You'll only make things worse if you show up again.
لن تؤدي زيارتك مرة أخرى إلا إلى تفاقم الأمور.
No matter what,
مهما حدث،
I have to bring Vivi back.
يجب أن أعيد فيفي.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
You're no longer Lan Hewei.
أنت لم تعد لان هيوي.
To her,
لها،
you're just a pretender
أنت مجرد متظاهر
who's up to no good.
من يخطط لشيء سيء.
Anything you do now is in vain.
كل ما تفعله الآن هو عبث.
You should focus on recovering.
يجب أن تركز على التعافي.
Where's Mr. Zhen?
أين السيد زين؟
I need to see him.
أحتاج لرؤيته.
He'll have a way. He'll support me.
سيكون لديه حل. سيدعمني.
He won't see you
لن يراك
until you're fully recovered.
حتى تتعافى تماماً.
Didn't I just say I wanted dessert?
ألم أقل للتو أنني أريد الحلوى؟
Did you not hear me,
ألم تسمعني؟
or did you just ignore me?
أم أنك تجاهلتني فحسب؟
Why do you always listen to me?
لماذا تستمع إليّ دائماً؟
Whatever I say, you just do it.
مهما قلت، عليك أن تفعله.
Are you willing to be someone's dog?
هل أنت مستعد لأن تكون كلباً لأحدهم؟
You said
أنت قلت
as long as I live here,
طالما أنني أعيش هنا،
I have to listen to you.
يجب أن أستمع إليك.
Besides,
بجانب،
you've helped me a lot.
لقد ساعدتني كثيراً.
This is the only way
هذا هو السبيل الوحيد
I can repay you.
أستطيع أن أسدد لك الدين.
So you're saying
إذن أنت تقول
you're doing this to repay me?
هل تفعل هذا لرد الجميل لي؟
But you're willing to
لكنك على استعداد لـ
do anything for Lan Hewei?
هل يمكنني فعل أي شيء من أجل لان هيوي؟
Say something!
قل شيئا!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Are you alright? I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
I said I don't need your help.
قلتُ إنني لست بحاجة إلى مساعدتك.
I'll take you to the hospital.
سآخذك إلى المستشفى.
Doctor,
طبيب،
how is she?
كيف حالها؟
I checked her out.
لقد راقبتها.
She's fine.
هي بخير.
It's a normal reaction in early pregnancy.
إنه رد فعل طبيعي في بداية الحمل.
Maybe it's because
ربما يكون ذلك بسبب
she's too emotional.
إنها عاطفية للغاية.
Pregnant?
حامل؟
She's pregnant?
هل هي حامل؟
Yes. She just got pregnant not long ago.
نعم. لقد حملت منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
Let her rest well.
دعها ترتاح جيداً.
When facing things, don't be too emotional.
عند مواجهة الأمور، لا تكن عاطفياً للغاية.
How could she be pregnant?
كيف يمكن أن تكون حاملاً؟
Why at this time?
لماذا في هذا الوقت تحديداً؟
The water temperature is just right.
درجة حرارة الماء مناسبة تماماً.
Drink a bit.
اشرب قليلاً.
During pregnancy,
أثناء الحمل،
you shouldn't drink alcohol.
لا ينبغي عليك شرب الكحول.
The doctor said
قال الطبيب
during pregnancy,
أثناء الحمل،
to control emotions
للسيطرة على المشاعر
during pregnancy.
أثناء الحمل.
Why are you so happy?
لماذا أنت سعيدٌ جداً؟
You don't think
ألا تعتقد
this baby is yours, do you?
هذا الطفل هو طفلك، أليس كذلك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I mean
أعني
this baby is not yours.
هذا الطفل ليس طفلك.
Don't flatter yourself.
لا تبالغ في تقدير نفسك.
Lu Xing,
لو شينغ,
I'm tired of you.
لقد سئمت منك.
Let's break up.
فلننفصل.
Take this card
خذ هذه البطاقة
and get as far away from me as you can.
وابتعد عني قدر استطاعتك.
I don't want to see you anymore.
لا أريد رؤيتك بعد الآن.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
You were in such a hurry just now.
كنتَ في عجلة من أمرك قبل قليل.
Why are you shy now?
لماذا أنت خجول الآن؟
Vivi, this is Mengmeng.
فيفي، هذه مينغمينغ.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
she will be your sister.
ستكون أختك.
Sister.
أخت.
Come on. Sit.
هيا، اجلس.
Mengmeng. Come. Vivi.
منغمينغ. تعالي. عيشي.
Come and sit.
تعال واجلس.
Come.
يأتي.
Look at the camera.
انظر إلى الكاميرا.
Don't blink.
لا ترمش.
Closer.
أقرب.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Vivi
أنت تعيش
Where are our parents?
أين والداي؟
They have something to do and haven't come back.
لديهم ما يفعلونه ولم يعودوا.
But
لكن
we'll celebrate your birthday with you.
سنحتفل بعيد ميلادك معك.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
we'll always celebrate your birthday with you.
سنحتفل دائمًا بعيد ميلادك معك.
You're 18 now,
أنت الآن في الثامنة عشرة من عمرك،
all grown up.
لقد كبروا جميعاً.
But no sneaking around in love,
لكن لا مجال للتسلل في الحب،
you have to tell me.
عليك أن تخبرني.
You're too naive,
أنت ساذج للغاية،
easy to get tricked.
من السهل أن يتم خداعك.
I've got to keep an eye out for you.
يجب أن أحرص على مراقبتك.
While I was unconscious,
بينما كنت فاقداً للوعي،
you disguised as me,
لقد تنكرت في هيئتي،
got close to my husband,
تقربت من زوجي،
set him up,
دبّر له مكيدة،
and took over Blue Crane.
واستحوذ على شركة بلو كرين.
How do you explain
كيف تشرح
all of this?
كل هذا؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
It's not like that.
الأمر ليس كذلك.
Then why did you get plastic surgery to look like me?
إذاً لماذا خضعتِ لعملية تجميل لتشبهيني؟
Tell me!
أخبرني!
I did it to get revenge.
فعلت ذلك للانتقام.
Vivi, where are you?
فيفي، أين أنتِ؟
Our deal isn't finished yet.
لم يتم الانتهاء من صفقتنا بعد.
Lin Moqing.
لين موكينج.
Lin Moqing, where are you?
لين موكينغ، أين أنت؟
You're not Vivi.
أنت لست فيفي.
You lied to me.
لقد كذبت عليّ.
No.
لا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You've gotten used to this name.
لقد اعتدت على هذا الاسم.
No.
لا.
You're not Lan Hewei.
أنت لست لان هيوي.
You've gotten used to this identity. No.
لقد اعتدتَ على هذه الهوية. لا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm not...
أنا لست كذلك...
Lan Hewei?
لان هيوي؟
Or Xu Meng?
أو شو منغ؟
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
It doesn't matter who I am.
لا يهم من أكون.
Your face is severely burned,
وجهك محروق بشدة،
and your vision is impaired.
وضعف في بصرك.
You won't be able to see clearly for a while.
لن تتمكن من الرؤية بوضوح لبعض الوقت.
Your sister is badly injured and unconscious.
أختك مصابة بجروح خطيرة وفاقدة للوعي.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I should have warned her earlier.
كان ينبغي عليّ أن أحذرها في وقت سابق.
I rushed over as soon as I got her call.
أسرعتُ إليها فور تلقي مكالمتها.
But I still couldn't save her.
لكنني مع ذلك لم أستطع إنقاذها.
She's still alive now.
إنها لا تزال على قيد الحياة الآن.
But the killer is still by her side.
لكن القاتل لا يزال بجانبها.
Are you just going to
هل ستفعل ذلك فقط؟
watch her in danger?
أشاهدها وهي في خطر؟
But with my current condition,
لكن مع حالتي الحالية،
how can I take revenge?
كيف يمكنني الانتقام؟
That's why you have to keep living.
لهذا السبب عليك أن تستمر في الحياة.
Only by living
فقط من خلال العيش
is there hope.
هل هناك أمل؟
As long as you want to,
طالما أردت ذلك،
I can help you take revenge.
أستطيع مساعدتك في الانتقام.
Why do you want to help me?
لماذا تريد مساعدتي؟
You just need to answer yes
كل ما عليك فعله هو الإجابة بنعم
or no.
أو لا.
I want revenge.
أريد الانتقام.
Are you satisfied?
هل أنت راضٍ؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
you are just Lan Hewei,
أنت مجرد لان هيوي،
not Xu Meng.
ليس شو منغ.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I am Lan Hewei.
أنا لان هيوي.